quiz = {
    1: {
        'question': 'Who is the archenemy of Aquaman?',
        'answer': 'Malefic',

    },
    2: {
        'question': 'Who does Dick Grayson take the name of Nightwing in honor of?',
        'answer': 'Superman and Batman'
    },
    3: {
        'question': 'Who originally killed Superman in the 1993 comic?',
        'answer': 'Doomsday'
    },
    4: {
        'question': 'Name the second most trusted hero in the Justice League?',
        'answer': 'Dick Grayson'
    },
    5: {
        'question': 'Who, in the DC universe, has a higher IQ than Batman?',
        'answer': 'Lex Luthor'
    },
    6: {
        'question': 'What is the first name of Iron man?',
        'answer': 'Tony'
    },
    7: {
        'question': 'Who is called the god of lightning in Avengers?',
        'answer': 'Thor'
    },
    8: {
        'question': 'Who carries a shield of American flag theme in Avengers?',
        'answer': 'Captain America'
    },
    9: {
        'question': 'Which avenger is green in color?',
        'answer': 'Hulk'
    },
    10: {
        'question': "Which avenger can change it's size?",
        'answer': 'Antman'
    },
    11: {
        'question': 'Which avenger is red in color and has a mind stone?',
        'answer': 'Vision'
    }
}
